No, it won't be all done. I mean
we've already started and the emphasis
obviously once we get closer to 26 will
be on 26, but the ground floor will be
laid, the foundation be laid,
start working with partners and and how
we're going to operate and kind of
timing everything else. So that when the
season's over, we then can have the
whole building including our coaching
staff really involved in the details of
how we're going to operate. Because the
last thing we want to do right now is
have any of our coaches worrying about
27. We have enough to worry about with
26 right now.
Will you treat Will you treat this like
a road game in terms of you'll come up,
bus down Saturday, and then stay the
night, and then Sunday is We'll view
this as a home game just with a long
commute to the office.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, that's fair. I mean that's
how we feel. I mean we think Listen,
number one we think a lot of our fans
will come down from Jacksonville. We
think we have a ton of fans in Orlando.
We also know that there's a ton of NFL
fans here. And then that with the
You combine that with the amount of
visiting teams that are going to want to
come to Jack to Orlando to watch their
team play. I mean it's a great
opportunity.
I mean as somebody with five kids, I
spend quite a bit of time on 95 and four
heading to Disney.
So we're familiar with it. I know my
family's excited about coming down and
watching the NFL and watching the
Jaguars play here. You mentioned it
already, but
do you have any idea about the logistics
of you guys bus down on a 84 or just be
like a normal road game or a flight? Do
you know that yet? Yeah, we're working
on that right now. We have a whole team
across the entire organization,
different departments working through
the logistics, the planning, because
it's not just the football operations
side, but it's also business. We have
sponsors, we have our fans, and we have
our players' families that we're going
to have to think about because they're
coming down. They all a lot of them have
small kids. And so it's a whole
organization effort to put the details
together. We're at the very beginning
stages. We'll spend a lot of time this
off season working on that so that we
can focus on 26 once the 26 season gets
here. And then at the end of that
going into the next off season, we'll
start looping in our coaches at that
point. Right now they're focused on 26.
How much of your organization do you
just have to embrace the whole thing?
This is obviously abnormal, but you guys
are used to that a little bit with
London, but I mean you got to do that to
be successful, right? To just embrace
it. We We look at it as an opportunity.
I mean it's I think it's a great
opportunity for us. At the end of the
day, you build a football team, you
engineer a football team that can play
anywhere. And we believe that. We
believe that we have the right head
coach in Liam and and the general
manager in James to engineer a team to
put together that will play Obviously,
we love
our home stadium and playing in
Jacksonville, but we play in London, we
go on the road, we had five West Coast
games, pretty sure we did okay last year
on the West Coast.
And we'll come to Orlando when it's time
and we'll be ready to play down here.
We're looking forward to playing in
front of all the fans
in Camping World. Yeah,
I think it's it's great and there's a
lot more to do and
we be done.
Yeah, so it's great day.
You mentioned having some connection to
the city of Orlando, spending a lot of
time here. How exciting is it to know
2027 you'll get to spend a little bit
more time here?
You have to rediscover. Yeah, so
Shad, how much room growth can there be
in the fan base
from what you guys have done in London,
but also just regionally here with
Orlando?
Yeah, I mean it's the the reality is the
state of Florida's population is
massive.
And
the NFL is an extremely popular sport in
the state of Florida.
We believe that there's an excess of
200,000
Jaguar fans who currently live in
Central Florida.
And
you can't define a fan simply by those
that go to the games, but in this
particular case, I think we'll be able
to deliver a much, much closer
connection between our fans in Central
Florida and
and the Jaguars. And to the degree
people, you know, fall in love with
Trevor Lawrence or if we have great
success down here, you know, they they
could end up continuing to be Jaguar
fans. But you know, keep in mind this is
this is necessary because of a
commitment
that Shad made to Jacksonville. If it
wasn't for that long-term commitment to
Jacksonville by Shad and and and the
city of Jacksonville, we wouldn't be
down here. You guys mentioned the Bucks
being supportive and helpful in this.
How important was it that they were
involved in this process?
You know, the important thing is you
want all 31 clubs supporting us.
And you know, they've been part of it.
Were they more part of it than other
teams and if so, how?
Well, a lot of it is is is logistics and
we had more conversations
with the Bucks
than we had with all the other teams
because of their proximity. You know, we
This This is a really important point.
The The The Orlando television market is
massive.
It's I think it's the 14th largest
television market in the country.
Not talking about just the city of
Orlando, Orlando television market.
That's what matters, okay?
There are portions of the Orlando
television market that are exclusive
territory for the Buccaneers.
There's portions of the Orlando
television market, Daytona, Melbourne,
that are exclusive territory of the
Jacksonville Jaguars.
There's portions of it where we share,
the Ocala market. And there's others
where any team can go in there. So when
you have that type of complexity, we've
had a radio affiliate in here since the
inaugural season. We've had a television
affiliate here since the inaugural
season. Our games get priority when
they're on broadcast TV down here. So it
is a market that we truly both operate
in. And because of that, we should have
had more conversations with the
Buccaneers than we would with the
Dolphins or any of the other teams. With
that said, could you see yourself not in
'28, but down the road playing a
preseason game in Orlando just to keep
that relationship
growing?
I I I I
don't know. I mean I don't
wouldn't project that. Preseason games
are changing quite a bit as you know.
>> Yeah. That would have to be coupled in
all likelihood with
practices that the teams would have
before the preseason game and
you know, you also have the reality of
we only you know, we we we've committed
Jacksonville and we don't necessarily
have the flexibility to other than those
games that are part of NFL the series to
be taking games all over the place.
Mark, for season ticket holders, what do
you know that you can share with
Jacksonville season ticket holders about
2027?
Well, Jacksonville season ticket holders
will get the first opportunity to buy
tickets.
And then from that point, we will
uh
continue a public sale.
In short order, we will be
announcing a way for individuals to
register interest in tickets.
Now, a lot of a lot of that's probably
going to come here from Central Florida,
not necessarily from from Jacksonville
and and we'll go from there. I mean it's
it's great to hear the optimism from
everybody down here. I know I know Shad
is is is confident. Um we want to have
an awesome year that year. We want the
stadium to be full. We want the
broadcast to be high quality. We want
the fan experience to be top notch. We
want the
performance on the field to be great.
And I think we we're all collectively
even more confident in Orlando, you
know, than we may have been a month ago.
Do you anticipate knowing how many home
games in Orlando there will be prior to
the normal NFL schedule or will that be
when the schedule is released in 2027?
>> Yeah, it's it's it's it's hard to
project that cuz there's still you you
even heard conversations coming out of
the meetings in Phoenix about maybe a
change to the schedule. So that would
that would impact that. What we know
today is
we have 10 home games
in 2027.
One preseason, nine regular season
We know one of the nine regular season
games is a game that the league is
taking from us
and taking it to London. It's our turn
to give up a home game. Beyond that,
there's no other commitments.
Do you know anything about primetime
games this year or next year because of
the situation? 42,000 capacity in
Jacksonville and then in Orlando. Are
you guys still have Would you be able to
involve Capacity
is not going to impact the number of
primetime games that we have in
Jacksonville.